[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3a8", "question": "What was the name of Alexander the Great's famous horse?", "answer": "Bucephalas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60136faf138175489539637a", "question": "In 2000, what character was elected U.S. President in the DC universe?", "answer": "Lex Luthor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c8a", "question": "\"Dead Men Don't Wear Plaid\" was the last film of what legendary costume designer?", "answer": "Edith Head", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba9e", "question": "What food company produces the cereals Count Chocula, Franken Berry, and Boo Berry?", "answer": "General Mills", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339229", "question": "Who is pictured with her eyes wide open on posters for Kubrick's \"Eyes Wide Shut\" movie?", "answer": "Nicole Kidman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab99daa21a8909e5c332d42", "question": "What was the original working title of the movie \"Help!\", starring the Beatles?", "answer": "Eight Arms To Hold You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe0e306fcbed638185eaa1f", "question": "Where is the United Nations (UN) Headquarters located?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0fc", "question": "Who created Gomez, Mortia and Uncle Fester as a cartoon?", "answer": "Charles Addams", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5ab", "question": "In which country would you find the Negev desert?", "answer": "Israel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b700", "question": "What sport is likely to cause pudendal nerve entrapment?", "answer": "Cycling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa3a8fc73aa70ea0b70adf", "question": "What is the oldest city in the world?", "answer": "Damascus (The capital of Syria has evidence of continuous habitation dating back at least 11,000 years)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133893b", "question": "What book mentions Colin Firth and Hugh Grant who both went on to star in the movie?", "answer": "The Bridget Jones's Diary", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a3b", "question": "What was the occupation of James Woods' character on the TV show \"Shark\"?", "answer": "Lawyer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf3e", "question": "Which word follows Juliet, Kilo and Lima?", "answer": "MIke", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a20c", "question": "What movie marked the first appearance of the mass murderer Jason Voorhees?", "answer": "Friday the 13th", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b8e2e662d71a53651029", "question": "The line \"All of this happened, more or less.\" starts what novel?", "answer": "\"Slaughterhouse-Five\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b293", "question": "What European country ruled Macau until December 20, 1999?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aad", "question": "What popular children\u2019s book did Forrest Gump keep in his briefcase?", "answer": "Curious George", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecd852ec223966ae8f88db", "question": "What 1980 film has a character named Lacey Underall?", "answer": "\"Caddyshack\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8d52f2b42d4a3561a9eff", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", What is the name of Francine\u2019s daughter?", "answer": "Jenny", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa6", "question": "What is a group of locusts called?", "answer": "Plague", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339352", "question": "How many seasons of the TV show \"The Beverly Hillbillies\" were filmed in black and white?", "answer": "Nine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396ed", "question": "What was the call sign of Tom Cruise's fighter pilot character in the movie \"Top Gun\"?", "answer": "Maverick", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c505", "question": "What is a group of apes called?", "answer": "A shrewdness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4d4", "question": "What is the better-known name of the card game \"Twenty-One\"?", "answer": "Blackjack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7c1", "question": "The viceroy butterfly is so named because of its mimicry of what other species?", "answer": "The monarch butterfly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4c3049076251badbeacf", "question": "Which unique pet did Calvin Coolidge have during his presidency?", "answer": "Raccoon -- Named Rachel, she might be the most well known pet.  She walked around on a leash and was the master of mischief.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc4e", "question": "The original Coca-Cola recipe is said to contain what controversial ingredient?", "answer": "Cocaine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "596df8ccf0cc2631d16a3c63", "question": "Crazy Horse and Sitting Bull were born in which US state?", "answer": "South Dakota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b569", "question": "What was the first Lifesaver flavor?", "answer": "Peppermint", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fefa4ab6ce05a3942286eb7", "question": "What is the name of the cat in the film \"Alien\"?", "answer": "Jonsey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfb4", "question": "In telephony, what do the initials ISDN stand for?", "answer": "Integrated Services for Digital Network", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b863", "question": "What is the highest possible bowling score in a game with no strikes?", "answer": "190", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cb70d48f96e155acab35d32", "question": "What is the most densely populated US state?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c21c", "question": "Traditional Scottish Highland Games feature which event where competitors throw a tapered 19 foot and 6 inch long log?", "answer": "Caber Toss", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a012", "question": "What director played a psychiatrist's psychiatrist on \"The Sopranos\"?", "answer": "Peter Bogdanovich", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d73", "question": "What ship was commanded by Jack Sparrow?", "answer": "Black Pearl", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f9f457caf848b908361b873", "question": "Who became president of Brazil in 2019?", "answer": "Jair Bolsonaro", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5921ff04a4edfd43a087add3", "question": "Which scientist wrote the book \"A Brief History of Time\"?", "answer": "Stephen Hawking", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be48", "question": "What word would best describe Port Salut?", "answer": "Cheese", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a26b", "question": "Who sang the song \"We Didn't Start the Fire\"?", "answer": "Billy Joel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b843e662d71a53651020", "question": "In what Broadway musical was the song \"Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas\" introduced?", "answer": "\"Meet Me in St. Louis\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5aab2e9358d116dab4aecb3f", "question": "Who played the inventor in the 1989 film \"Honey, I Shrunk the Kids\"?", "answer": "Rick Moranis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ed4", "question": "What SNL cast member voiced \"Waldo\" in Van Halen's \"Hot for Teacher\" video?", "answer": "Phil Hartman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b80e", "question": "What is \"nori\" made from?", "answer": "Seaweed", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5be5812d5415ba52ed6f0abe", "question": "What year did H. G. Well publish the comic novel \"The History of Mr Polly\"?", "answer": "1910", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba8c", "question": "How much does it cost to purchase Boardwalk in the standard game of Monopoly?", "answer": "$400", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e2d", "question": "Who is Ben Stiller's mother?", "answer": "Anne Meara", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cdd", "question": "How many years was Robinson Crusoe shipwrecked on his island before being rescued?", "answer": "28", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd6658aa5bfecdd737e0860", "question": "What is the most common birthday?", "answer": "September 9", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6bb49fb6c85e9e634ff53", "question": "Which American female vocalist had a hit in 1985 with \"We Don't Need Another Hero\"?", "answer": "Tina Turner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5906835cff9c0647b50a80a6", "question": "Alec Baldwin started hosting which ABC show on June 26, 2016?", "answer": "Match Game", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a98e361d1b4d384d5d693", "question": "Which major lake is near the Ponderosa Ranch in the TV show \"Bonanza\"?", "answer": "Lake Tahoe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c7f", "question": "Who was the first African American woman to host a TV show?", "answer": "Oprah Winfrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ac2", "question": "Who first published \"Little Red Riding Hood\"?", "answer": "Charles Perrault", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b452", "question": "Which famed hunter, scout, and showman of the Old West nicknamed his rifle \"Lucretia Borgia\"?", "answer": "Buffalo Bill", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b76e", "question": "\"Old Scratch\" is a nickname for whom?", "answer": "Satan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015dfb3fe83fe1f2a824b7d", "question": "What ancestor of brass knuckles did ancient warriors use?", "answer": "Cestus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c76b", "question": "The curlew is a type of what?", "answer": "Bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc25", "question": "In what year was Wikipedia officially launched?", "answer": "2001", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a899c2e60d398dc9cf7a6a5", "question": "Vesta is the Roman goddess of what?", "answer": "Hearth, home and family", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1fd", "question": "In what city did the First and Second Continental Congresses meet?", "answer": "Philadelphia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1e", "question": "What city was the setting for the TV show \"Perfect Strangers\"?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338941", "question": "What creatures in \"The Lord of the Rings\" are referred to as goblins in the book \"The Hobbit\"?", "answer": "Orcs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133940b", "question": "What is the name of Drew Barrymore's character in the 1982 movie E.T. the Extra Terrestrial\"?", "answer": "Gertie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59029fb8cad1ec93f27df763", "question": "Who was Strongbow cider named after?", "answer": "Richard de Clare", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9ea", "question": "What is it that turns red litmus paper blue?", "answer": "Basic solution", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5c7", "question": "Ageusia is the loss of which sense?", "answer": "Taste", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c2a", "question": "What American author created the characters of Rip Van Winkle and Ichabod Crane?", "answer": "Washington Irving", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdab34a0b8cce1e6fda7044", "question": "What do you call filo pastry stuffed with chopped nuts and honey, or syrup?", "answer": "Baklava", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a693", "question": "Buenos Aires is the capital of what country?", "answer": "Argentina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fbaed2f0738315b1fb74e2f", "question": "In what year did the first president of Kenya, Jomo Kenyatta, die?", "answer": "1978", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e804aade59ea584496fea6", "question": "In which sport must the ball have a diameter of at least 42.67 millimetres and weigh no less than 45.93 grams?", "answer": "Golf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b66a", "question": "Which Pac-Man ghost appears first on the arcade game's list?", "answer": "Shadow (Blinky)", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab1bb0baab681b0929219b", "question": "Which Canadian city is host to the Canadian International Autoshow?", "answer": "Toronto", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7fa", "question": "What are the only two South American countries that do not border Brazil?", "answer": "Chile and Ecuador", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae28", "question": "In which decade was the Panama Canal completed?", "answer": "1910s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f1684df7c52aae91cc07c5", "question": "Selaphobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Light flashes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338893", "question": "What is heaven to fallen Norse warriors?", "answer": "Valhalla", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c410877e98cb9777899a", "question": "What city requires aspiring cab drivers to undergo years of training?", "answer": "London", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399ce", "question": "In what 2006 film does a family travel in a VW microbus to get to a beauty pageant?", "answer": "Little Miss Sunshine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "592eb0ccf83302ff91e464a0", "question": "What year was the luxury brand \"Tiffany & Co.\" founded?", "answer": "1837", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b571c8667df192a942e3375", "question": "Who is Edson Arantes do Nascimento more widely known as?", "answer": "Pele", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339687", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who is Chief Wiggum's wife?", "answer": "Sarah Wiggum", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a56", "question": "What old TV puppet show was hosted by \"Buffalo\" Bob Smith?", "answer": "Howdy Doody", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133923a", "question": "What superhero sidekick is known as Boy Wonder?", "answer": "Robin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b56801dd7bf43be5e7d0", "question": "What does \"dachshund\" mean?", "answer": "Badger dog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390b5", "question": "Who was the wife of King Cepheus of \u00c6thiopia?", "answer": "Cassiopeia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe69e3620565ad31a57c780", "question": "What was the real name of the Confederate ironclad ship that went to battle with the USS Monitor?", "answer": "CSS Virginia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eb09df83302ff91e4649e", "question": "Who directed the 1972 film \"The Godfather\"?", "answer": "Francis Ford Coppola", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fc", "question": "Who was James Garfield's vice president?", "answer": "Chester A. Arthur", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c75c", "question": "What number does the letter \"V\" with a bar over it represent in Roman numerals?", "answer": "5,000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbf9", "question": "What flavor was the Twinkie's original filling?", "answer": "Banana", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a126", "question": "Which Paul Simon album won a Grammy for album of the year in 1987?", "answer": "Graceland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bebb", "question": "The South Beach Diet is named for a section of what city?", "answer": "Miami Beach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b592", "question": "What does the abbreviation SUV stand for?", "answer": "Sport Utility Vehicle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a38e", "question": "What is the only officially bilingual province in Canada?", "answer": "New Brunswick", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5904a3dfcf93664eb10486c0", "question": "Not including spin-offs or tie-ins, how many issues were released as part of the original \"Strangers in Paradise\" series that ended in 2007?", "answer": "90", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a600", "question": "Which state is nicknamed the \"Empire State\"?", "answer": "New York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b825", "question": "What Fortune 500 company was name for a Herman Melville character?", "answer": "Starbucks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f1b", "question": "What author created the land of Pellucidar?", "answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af80", "question": "Who did Dwight Eisenhower defeat twice in presidential elections during the 1950s?", "answer": "Adlai Stevenson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b5718a867df192a942e3361", "question": "To a golfer what is a \"Frosty\"?", "answer": "Score of 8 on a hole", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1be", "question": "Lesley Hornby became more famous as who?", "answer": "Twiggy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be9b", "question": "In what Olympic sport is the \"clean and jerk\" event held?", "answer": "Weightlifting", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9cc", "question": "In which modern day country would you find the region known as Transylvania?", "answer": "Romania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c81a", "question": "In what part of the body would you find sebum?", "answer": "The skin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab957c86faa38a764be516", "question": "How many cylinders did the first generation Dodge Viper have?", "answer": "10", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339128", "question": "Who composed the 1877 opera \"Samson and Delilah\"?", "answer": "Camille Saint-Saens", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe523921bf59ab7d2e380f0", "question": "In which country would you find fried meatballs served with potatoes and gravy called frikadeller?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a162", "question": "Kappelkoff is the real surname of which actress?", "answer": "Doris Day", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe65db11f3c0ead6880d61f", "question": "Where was the treaty signed ending the Russo-Japanese War?", "answer": "Portsmouth, New Hampshire", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea438bff048f679a45ab82", "question": "What is the inherent voltage of lithium?", "answer": "2.7 volts", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ca", "question": "What year was the movie \"Aliens\" released?", "answer": "1986", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8e7", "question": "Which great American inventor died in October, 1931?\u00a0", "answer": "Thomas Edison", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe51e681bf59ab7d2e380e1", "question": "Jambon is the French word for what food?", "answer": "Ham", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a63a", "question": "West Virginia has a shoreline along which ocean?", "answer": "None", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338951", "question": "What job does Joe teach to Pip in Great Expectations?", "answer": "Blacksmith", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a651", "question": "In which US state can one visit the Appomattox Court House National Historical Park?", "answer": "Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c88c", "question": "What does the Binet-Simon scale measure?", "answer": "Intelligence", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397fa", "question": "With which group would you associate the songs \"Light My Fire\" and \"Hello I Love You\"?", "answer": "The Doors", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad05", "question": "Where were the 1996 Summer Olympics held?", "answer": "Atlanta, Georgia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa55bbc73aa70ea0b70b26", "question": "In which Asian city is the historic waterfront called The Bund?", "answer": "Shanghai", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600244e04be4723ccac221a9", "question": "What artist's portrait of George Washington is the basis for the US $1 bill?", "answer": "The portrait on the current U.S. one-dollar bill is an unfinished work by the artist\u00a0Gilbert Stuart. It was painted in 1796.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d4", "question": "What is the atomic number of iodine?", "answer": "53", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c57e", "question": "In relation to location, what does the abbreviation GPS stand for?", "answer": "Global Positioning System", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f18", "question": "What author created Earthsea?", "answer": "Ursula K. Le Guin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d7", "question": "How many diagonals does a triangle have?", "answer": "None", "category": "science"}, {"id": "592eaf96f83302ff91e46494", "question": "What are juvenile goats called?", "answer": "Kids", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600f716ea9e54d890926f6e0", "question": "In which country is the Troi-Rivieres bridge?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ec6", "question": "In what band did Roger, Andy, and John Taylor all play?", "answer": "Duran Duran", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a36b", "question": "What country administers Greenland?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e69", "question": "According to the prologue to \"Romeo and Juliet\", in what city do the pair of star-cross'd lovers take their life?", "answer": "Verona", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd6e", "question": "The most traditional Greek feta cheese is made from what animal's milk?", "answer": "Sheep's milk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010c5df0775fa611bce67cd", "question": "The Chang Building in Bangkok, Thailand, was designed to look like what?", "answer": "Elephant -- AKA the Elephant Building, the skyscraper was intended to reflect the importance of elephants in Thai culture.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f169b5f7c52aae91cc07d3", "question": "Who played \"Hawkeye\" in the 1970 film \"MASH\"?", "answer": "Donald Sutherland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a342", "question": "What kind of a doll grabs Robbie and drags him under his bed in the 1982 film \"Poltergeist\"?", "answer": "A clown doll", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea353bff048f679a45aaff", "question": "Which planet is known as the Evening Star?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fa", "question": "What year did James Garfield start and end his presidency?", "answer": "1881", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e43", "question": "What bestseller tells the story of the fishing boat \"Andrea Gail\"?", "answer": "The Perfect Storm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c333", "question": "How much of the daily recommended calcium intake does a glass of milk contain?", "answer": "39%", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c54b", "question": "What is the common name for iron oxide, which appears after iron has been exposed to air and water?", "answer": "Rust", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b598", "question": "Which band's song was the 1 billionth iTunes download?", "answer": "Coldplay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdc11a0469bb8041d07a077", "question": "What Indian spice that grows in pods is used to make chai tea?", "answer": "Cardamom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ab99d1f21a8909e5c332d3e", "question": "What was Harold Lloyd Jenkins' stage name?", "answer": "Conway Twitty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600cc2286de0eb824d4052e4", "question": "What U.S. state's official dessert is Smith Island Cake?", "answer": "Smith Island lies about 12 miles off the coast of Maryland in Chesapeake Bay and is home to the its tantalizing state dessert.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2c1", "question": "In atmospheres, what is the equivalent of 760 milimeters of Mercury (mmHg)?", "answer": "1 atm", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfd7", "question": "What is the NATO phonetic alphabet word for \"R\"?", "answer": "Romeo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d7", "question": "Who were Bobby Hatfield and Bill Medley?", "answer": "The Righteous Brothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58c89d41011619dd6d415484", "question": "What book did Butters write as a sequel to \"Scrotie McBoogerballs\"?", "answer": "The Poop That Took a Pee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d6", "question": "Who was the first president of the Academy of Motion of Picture Arts and Sciences?", "answer": "Douglas Fairbanks Jr.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefc1176ce05a3942286f0e", "question": "In the Bourne film series, what is Jason Bourne's real name?", "answer": "David Webb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab34", "question": "Off what country lies the island of Zanzibar?", "answer": "Tanzania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f95", "question": "What rock band brought suit in 1994 claiming that Ticketmaster was an illegal monopoly?", "answer": "Pearl Jam", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c08c", "question": "What is the American equivalent of the Irish Poitin?", "answer": "Moonshine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec8557ec223966ae8f8804", "question": "Which famous golf player was nicknamed \"Golden Bear\"?", "answer": "Jack Nicklaus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133960d", "question": "What movie gave us the tagline \"The first casualty of war is innocence\"?", "answer": "Platoon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c205", "question": "What year was the US an Olympic Games host for the first time?", "answer": "1904", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0f4", "question": "Who had a hit with the song and album \"Sweet Dreams (Are Made Of This)\"?", "answer": "Eurythmics", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c975", "question": "What is rainfall measured with?", "answer": "Ombrometer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a21a", "question": "Craig Phillips was the first winner of which TV reality show?", "answer": "UK's \"Big Brother\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388eb", "question": "What is the dot in the \"i\" called?", "answer": "A tittle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0d3", "question": "What former country was Martina Navratilova born in?", "answer": "Czechoslovakia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cd40d8c685cf15b733e9893", "question": "In the Simpsons what is the discount on the chocolate in the \"Land of Chocolate\"?", "answer": "Half Price", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937ee0308d98002fdd633cf", "question": "What is a strong aversion to beards known as?", "answer": "Pogonophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7e5", "question": "What element of the periodic table is named for a Jewish woman?", "answer": "Meitnerium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5904a4a2cf93664eb10486c5", "question": "Early on in the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", what type of car does Freddie brag about driving?", "answer": "A Porsche", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab2f", "question": "Which ocean is the region of Melanesia located in?", "answer": "Pacific", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea3674ff048f679a45ab0e", "question": "What vegetable grows fast enough that you can hear it?", "answer": "Rhubarb", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a737", "question": "Which US state is home to Craters of the Moon National Monument?", "answer": "Idaho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a35e", "question": "Where is the International Court of Justice?", "answer": "The Hague", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe768aaeec85e375820b2a4", "question": "What country once had a banknote that featured a woman riding a shark?", "answer": "Cook Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d52", "question": "What Herman Melville character always answers \"I would prefer not to\" whenever his boss asks him to work?", "answer": "Bartleby the Scrivener", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeec", "question": "In which year did the Japanese attack Pearl Harbor?", "answer": "1941", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe69ae020565ad31a57c757", "question": "What was the first non-axis jet plane to see combat?", "answer": "Gloster Meteor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60121b2963c99d48cd169b0c", "question": "A soniferous object produces what?", "answer": "Sound -- Soniferous animals don\u2019t just make sound, it\u2019s an especially loud and far-reaching sound.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b654", "question": "The hymn for what branch of the US military begins with the line: \"From the halls of Montezuma\"?", "answer": "Marine Corps", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393f2", "question": "Who sang the title song for the 1978 suspense film \"Eyes of Laura Mars\"?", "answer": "Barbra Streisand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abc0", "question": "Tirana is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Albania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59a7f64f6f5f79087132fb43", "question": "Which actress who played Alia Atreides in 1984's \"Dune\" and went on to star in 1998's \"Urban Legend\"?", "answer": "Alicia Witt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8f80301dd7bf43be5e83c", "question": "Cynophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Dogs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba1e", "question": "What does \"dakota\" mean in the Sioux language?", "answer": "Friend", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc1e", "question": "What year was the Rubik's Cube invented?", "answer": "1974", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c868", "question": "What is the heaviest internal organ in the human body?", "answer": "The liver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fc854a6abc30a8194e188a9", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Jaws\"?", "answer": "Peter Benchley", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b01b", "question": "Who was US's first Postmaster General?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b62f", "question": "In the Western Union's alphabet what is the letter \"C\" known as?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c914", "question": "What is the atomic number of magnesium?", "answer": "12", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb0e", "question": "What common cooking ingredient gets its name from the French words meaning \"sour wine\"?", "answer": "Vinegar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad1", "question": "What do nephologists study?", "answer": "Clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fec88acec223966ae8f8821", "question": "LCS is the acronym for a professional eSports league centered around which game?", "answer": "League of Legends", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab1b7fbaab681b0929219a", "question": "What is BMW's name short for?", "answer": "Bayerische Motoren Werke", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c576", "question": "Which planet in our solar system is known as the Earth's twin?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4b9949076251badbeac5", "question": "The Iditarod Trail Sled Dog Race was inspired in part by what event?", "answer": "A diphtheria outbreak -- In 1925, several teams of mush dogs relayed a serum for diphtheria from Seward to Nome, Alaska.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a613", "question": "Name the largest landlocked country in Europe?", "answer": "Belarus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b594", "question": "When was the game \"Scrabble\" first released?", "answer": "1948", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393d0", "question": "How many guns does Travis buy in the movie \"Taxi Driver\"?", "answer": "4", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339944", "question": "What actress was Tom Cruise\u2019s first wife?", "answer": "Mimi Rogers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010caa10775fa611bce67fc", "question": "In American politics, what does GOP stand for?", "answer": "GOP, another name for the Republican Party, stands for Grand Old Party.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d0a", "question": "What movie's first sequel featured the subtitle \"The Edge of Reason\"?", "answer": "Bridget Jones's Diary", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c4b6877e98cb977789a4", "question": "Which country\u2019s flag has the most colors?", "answer": "Belize", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de2", "question": "What \"Desperate Housewives\" creator broke into TV as a personal assistant to actress Dixie Carter?", "answer": "Marc Cherry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395c2", "question": "In The Simpsons, what kind of factory is next door to where the Krusty the Clown show is taped?", "answer": "A box factory", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa416fc73aa70ea0b70b0f", "question": "Which Hawaiian island is entirely privately owned?", "answer": "Ni'ihau (The island was purched by wealthy Scottish plantation owners from King Kamehameha V in 1864 for $10,000 in gold.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a579", "question": "What is the capital of the state of Texas?", "answer": "Austin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d47119f8e329de4f877898", "question": "How many standard bottles of wine are there in a Nebuchadnezzar?", "answer": "20 Bottles", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c6d", "question": "What are the names of the four Musketeers?", "answer": "Athos, Aramis, Porthos and D\u2019artagnan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133993a", "question": "Who voices the character of Bart Simpson on the TV show \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "Nancy Cartwright", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133929e", "question": "In \"Ferris Bueller's Day Off\", who is the \"Sausage King of Chicago\"?", "answer": "Abe Froman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c6", "question": "Who did agent John Drake work for in \"Secret Agent\"?", "answer": "NATO", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601debe96b1208747aa7e9d7", "question": "Which famous entrepreneur is credited with inventing the weekend?", "answer": "Henry Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b077", "question": "What was the last name of Civil Rights activist Malcolm X?", "answer": "Little", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bfe0020b668d7dfe168b5bf", "question": "Which brand of beer does Homer Simpson drink regularly?", "answer": "Duff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cc6", "question": "What synthpop instrumental was the biggest hit for \"Hot Butter\"?", "answer": "Popcorn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd664cfa5bfecdd737e0858", "question": "What animal does cashmere come from?", "answer": "Goat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff66e3852a821ff76ae8b1a", "question": "What do you eat when you accept that you're wrong about something?", "answer": "\"Crow\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59049aaecf93664eb1048699", "question": "Who was Joe\u2019s co-creator for the character of Superman?", "answer": "Jerry Siegel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad7ea43b24f84e0b9f9ffd2", "question": "What is a figure with eight equal sides called?", "answer": "Regular Octagon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59068058ff9c0647b50a808b", "question": "Who wrote and directed the 1973 film \"Westworld\" that was used as the basis for the 2016 HBO TV series by the same name?", "answer": "Michael Crichton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133914c", "question": "Who was the Roman equivalent of the Greek god Hephaestus?", "answer": "Vulcan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5b174691bb2d29f81593b708", "question": "What were the name of the two space shuttles in the 1998 film \"Armageddon\"?", "answer": "Freedom and Independence", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c3e986bebfabb9c85d8a96b", "question": "Who released the album \"Tuesday Night Music Club\" in 1993?", "answer": "Sheryl Crow", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c01b", "question": "What three letter word means \"the front of a ship\"?", "answer": "Bow", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be9f", "question": "What candy bar was named for a beloved horse of the Mars family?", "answer": "Snickers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e72cc9ed0874f1a5e2d1c24", "question": "What is Michael J. Fox\u2019s middle name?", "answer": "Andrew", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339edf", "question": "What position was first held by Trygve Lie?", "answer": "UN Secretary General", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc34", "question": "Which US state is home to CNN?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f6eb9a9e54d890926f6c9", "question": "From what did the Caribbean derive its name?", "answer": "Indigenous people - The word \"Carib\" refers to one of the Amerindian groups on the islands when they were discovered by Europeans.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe9f1f4ff048f679a45aab4", "question": "What is the functional unit of heredity?", "answer": "Gene", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339308", "question": "In the 1987 movie \"Fatal Attraction\", what animal did the obsessed woman cook on the stove?", "answer": "A rabbit", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b7b1e662d71a53651016", "question": "Who painted \"Madonna of the Rosary\", in which St. Dominic has been given a rosary by \"the Virgin\"?", "answer": "Caravaggio", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad7ec7cb24f84e0b9f9ffe7", "question": "Who made the song \"Bad Case of Loving You\" popular?", "answer": "Robert Palmer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a99e", "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano \"Lamington\"?", "answer": "Papua New Guinea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6574bae7e414034b5aedb", "question": "Where did Barack Obama teach constitutional law?", "answer": "University of Chicago", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e9b", "question": "Whose crime was witnessed only by Cindy Lou Who?", "answer": "The Grinch's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b77", "question": "What patriotic anthem composed by Irving Berlin includes the lyrics \"Stand beside her and guide her\"?", "answer": "God Bless America", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae43", "question": "How old was John F. Kennedy when he was assassinated?", "answer": "46", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a831", "question": "The powerful Inca empire had its capital seat at Cuzco in what modern-day South American country?", "answer": "Peru", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad8c", "question": "Where was the Salvation Army's Christmas collection kettle first introduced?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a4a991561d1b4d384d5d696", "question": "How long was the TV show \"Gunsmoke\" between 1955 and 1961?", "answer": "30 minutes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7f7", "question": "What sauce is used in traditional eggs Benedict?", "answer": "Hollandaise", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b357", "question": "Albert DeSalvo is better known as whom?", "answer": "The Boston Strangler", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5909ccedbb53d1af658864e5", "question": "What branch of Christianity introduced the Advent calendar?", "answer": "German Lutherans", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff51215ff04d658268c92cd", "question": "Who was the first American casualty in the American Revolutionary War?", "answer": "Crispus Attucks\u00a0was the first person killed in the Boston massacre and is widely considered to be the first American casualty.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a2c", "question": "Jenny McCarthy and Carmen Electra were both hosts on what MTV game show during the 1990's?", "answer": "Singled Out", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133959e", "question": "Who appears alongside Jim Carrey in the 1994 movie \"Dumb and Dumber\"?", "answer": "Jeff Daniels", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b92", "question": "What wealthy comic-book title character keeps his mansion tidy with the help of a robot maid, Irona?", "answer": "Richie Rich", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5cefc060948005ec986edcda", "question": "Who is the first member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Heejin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60173d2b44491cbd7c5a17aa", "question": "What is the oldest active international airline?", "answer": "KLM Royal Dutch Airlines -- Founded in 1919, KLM is also the\u00a0oldest airline in the world\u00a0still operating under its original name.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a42", "question": "In 1990, Jennifer Aniston played the Jennifer Grey role in a short-lived TV show based on what movie?", "answer": "Ferris Bueller's Day Off", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e95", "question": "What movie did the villain Amon Goeth appear in?", "answer": "Schindler's List", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9c0", "question": "Lake Vanern is the largest lake in which country?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1ec", "question": "What is added to cognac and absinthe to make a Sazerac cocktail?", "answer": "Sugar cube and Peychaud's bitters", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecd1e4ec223966ae8f88c1", "question": "While filming \"Guardians of the Galaxy\", what did director James Gunn give out as rewards to his actors and crew?", "answer": "Play-Doh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe7", "question": "Which US president was born in Tampico, Illinois?", "answer": "Ronald Reagan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339633", "question": "What Sergio Leone spaghetti western is a remake of Kurosawa's \"Yojimbo\"?", "answer": "A Fistful of Dollars", "category": "entertainment"}]